okay i've shown this effect in the past
but i'm going to do this again
because it's been a while go ahead and
turn on this guy
mood audio there we go
okay now we come over here
and we go like this put red in the
middle
black on the outside
connection switch it
red to the outside black to the middle
nothing next plate
nothing next plate nothing outer plate
it's connected okay switch
black to the outside electrode
that plate's connected that plate's
connected
and that plate's connected reset
okay but if i go to the electrode and i
go to the water
or i go to one of the insulators
nothing so
the gel cell is acting like
a diode
you